Guide to the KUHT Records 1997-006
University of Houston Libraries Special Collections
- Publications
  - Newspaper Clippings - KUHT, 1994 (Box 455, Folder 38)
  - Newspaper Clippings - KUHT, 1995 (Box 455, Folder 39)
  - Newspaper Clippings - KUHT, 1996 (Box 455, Folder 40)
  - Newspaper Clippings - KUHT, 1997 (Box 455, Folder 41)
  - Newspaper Clippings - KUHT, 1998 (Box 455, Folder 42)
  - Newspaper Clippings - KUHT, 1999 (Box 455, Folder 43)
  - Newspaper Clippings - KUHT, 2000 (Box 455, Folder 44)
  - Newspaper Clippings - KUHT, 2001 (Box 455, Folder 45)
  - Newspaper Clippings - KUHT, 2002 (Box 455, Folder 46)
  - Newspaper Clippings - KUHT, 2003 (Box 455, Folder 47)
  - KUHF/KUHT Program Guide Collection Information (Box 455, Folder 48)
  - KUHF Program Guide/Radio Guide, July 1985 (Box 455, Folder 49)
  - KUHF Program Guide/Radio Guide, October 1987 (Box 455, Folder 50)
  - KUHF Program Guide/Radio Guide, August 1992 (Box 455, Folder 51)
  - KUHF Program Guide/Radio Guide, May-June 2002, September-October 2002 (Box 455, Folder 52)
  - KUHF Program Guide/Radio Guide, January-May 2003 (Box 455, Folder 53)
  - KUHF Program Guide/Radio Guide, June-October 2003 (Box 455, Folder 54)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, March-December 1962 (Box 456, Folder 1)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-December 1963 (Box 456, Folder 2)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-May 1964, September-December 1964 (Box 456, Folder 3)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January 1965, July-December 1965 (Box 456, Folder 4)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-December 1966 (Box 456, Folder 5)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-December 1967 (Box 456, Folder 6)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-December 1968 (Box 456, Folder 7)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-December 1969 (Box 456, Folder 8)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-December 1970 (Box 456, Folder 9)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-December 1971 (Box 456, Folder 10)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-December 1972 (Box 456, Folder 11)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-September 1973, November-December 1973 (Box 456, Folder 12)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-December 1974 (Box 456, Folder 13)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-December 1975 (Box 456, Folder 14)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-December 1976 (Box 456, Folder 15)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-December 1977 (Box 456, Folder 16)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-December 1978 (Box 456, Folder 17)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-December 1979 (Box 456, Folder 18)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-December 1980 (Box 456, Folder 19)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-December 1981 (Box 456, Folder 20)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-December 1982 (Box 456, Folder 21)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-December 1983 (Box 456, Folder 22)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-December 1984 (Box 456, Folder 23)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-December 1985 (Box 456, Folder 24)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-October 1986, December 1986 (Box 456, Folder 25)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-December 1987 (Box 456, Folder 26)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-September 1988, November-December 1988 (Box 456, Folder 27)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-June 1989, August-December 1989 (Box 456, Folder 28)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-December 1990 (Box 456, Folder 29)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, February-April 1991, September-December 1991 (Box 456, Folder 30)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-August 1992, October-November 1992 (Box 456, Folder 31)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, February 1993, June-July 1993 (Box 456, Folder 32)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January 1994, March 1994, May-December 1994 (Box 456, Folder 33)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-December 1995 (Box 456, Folder 34)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-December 1996 (Box 457, Folder 1)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-December 1997 (Box 457, Folder 2)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-December 1998 (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-December 1999 (Box 457, Folder 4)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-December 2000 (Box 457, Folder 5)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January-December 2001 (Box 457, Folder 6)
  - Program Preview/Public Times/Program Guide/The Guide, January 2002, March-December 2002 (Box 457, Folder 7)
  - KUHT Program Schedule, 1953 (Box 457, Folder 8)
  - KUHT Program Schedule, 1954 (Box 457, Folder 9)
  - KUHT Program Schedule, 1955 (Box 457, Folder 10)
  - KUHT Program Schedule, 1956 (Box 457, Folder 11)
  - KUHT Program Schedule, 1957 (Box 457, Folder 12)
  - KUHT Program Schedule, 1958 (Box 457, Folder 13)
  - KUHF Publicity, Promotional Correspondence (Box 457, Folder 14-15)
  - Television Instructional Programming, Miscellaneous Universities (Box 457, Folder 16)
  - The Audience for Educational Television, October 1959 (Box 457, Folder 17)
  - The President's Report, 1992-1993, 1995, 1996-1997 (Box 457, Folder 18)
  - UH Alumline, Winter 1993, Summer 1996, Spring 1997 (Box 457, Folder 19)
  - UH Communication Arts - Role of Production..., Children's Programming... (Box 457, Folder 20)
  - Yearbook, Broadcasting Cable, 1980 (Box 457, Folder 21)
- Miscellaneous
  - Guest Book, 1990-1992 (Box 458, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 458, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Articles (Box 458, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 458, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Reports (Box 458, Folder 5)
  - Production Promo Reels - Inventory and Storage Correspondence (Box 458, Folder 6)
  - Production Promo Reels - Inventory, 1989-1992 (Box 458, Folder 7)
  - Production Promo Reels - Inventory Beta Tape (Box 458, Folder 8)
  - Production Promo Reels - Inventory VHS Tape (Box 458, Folder 9)
  - Production Promo Reels - Inventory Cassette (Box 458, Folder 10)
  - Application for Official Texas Historial Marker, 2011 (Box 458, Folder 11)
- Scrapbooks
  - 1950-1953 (Box 459)
  - 1953-1956 (Box 459)
  - 1957-1964 (Box 460)
  - 1965-1968 (Box 461)
  - 1968-1969 (Box 461)
  - 1969-1971 (Box 462)
  - 1970 (Box 462)
  - 1970 (Box 463)
  - 1971 (Box 463)
  - 1980-1981 (Box 464)
  - Compendium, 1976-1979 (Box 464, Folder 1)
  - 1982-1983 (Box 465)
  - 1984 (Box 465)
  - 1985 (Box 466)
  - 1986 (Box 466)
  - April 1985-May 13, 1989 (Box 466, Folder 1)
  - 1987-1988 (Box 467)
  - 1989-1990 (Box 467)
  - 1990 (Box 468)
  - 1991 (Box 468)
  - January-April 1992 (Box 469)
  - May-December 1992 (Box 469)
  - 1993 (Box 470)
  - 1994 (Box 471)
  - Separation Sheets (Box 471, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1955-1961, undated (Box 471, Folder 2)
  - January 1971-February 1973 (Ovs box 472)
  - May 1973-May 1975 (Ovs box 473)
  - April 1974-August 1975 (Ovs box 474)
  - September 1975-December 1976 (Ovs box 475)
  - Critical Issues, 1967-1968, 1968-1969 (Ovs box 476)
  - Critical Issues, 1969-1970, 1970-1971, 1971-1972 (Ovs box 477)
  - Critical Issues, 1972-1973, 1973-1974 (Ovs box 478)
- Unprocessed materials
  242 linear feet of unprocessed boxes arrived on July 11, 2014. An additional accrual arrived in September 2015.
  - Miscellanous OVS (Drawer Z.7, Ovs folder 2)
    Fine Arts Center plans, KUHT Daily Cougar news clippings, Dr. Robert Parker board